mightymagoo.com 2011-06-24

# Privacy Policy » Mighty Magoo

## Privacy Policy

**MightyMagoo.com Privacy Policy**

**Updated:** December 9, 2010

This Privacy Policy explains what information Duck Play LLC (the “Company” or “we”) collects from individuals who visit the MightyMagoo.com website (the “Site” or “MightyMagoo”) and/or participate in the resources offered by MightyMagoo (“User(s)” or “you”). This Policy also explains how the Company uses and maintains that information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first email [MightyMagoo Support](mailto:support@mightymagoo.com)

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the MightyMagoo home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the MightyMagoo home page.

**  
This Policy applies only to Information collected on MightyMagoo and not to information collected or obtained from other sources.**

We collect two kinds of information (“Information”) through the Site. The first kind is information that can identify you as a specific individual – such as your name and email address (“PII”). **We only collect PII when you have contacted us directly or forwarded content from our site to someone else**. (See “Collection of Personally Identifiable Information” below). The second kind of information is the kind of non-personally identifiable information (“NPII”) collected and stored automatically by many websites. It includes, for example, information about your Internet service provider, operating system, type of browser, geographic location, and pages viewed on MightyMagoo. Although this information is related to you, it is not associated with your PII and cannot be linked to you personally. If you register to play Premium Games, the NPII collected may also include your internet protocol and HTML information about the content of web pages you visit.

**If you do not want your Information to continue to be collected and used as provided in this Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Site again.**

Premium Game players (“Premium Users”) have access to the Premium Games at no charge in exchange for their agreement to install the MightyMagoo Software (the “Software”) on their computers or other computing device. The Software allows us to provide a Premium User with a limited amount of text link and banner advertisements based on the web content viewed by that User. No PII is collected through the Software. However, the Software does track HTML on the web pages the user visits as well as URLs, and/or search queries in order to deliver ads.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

PII is collected by MightMagoo **only when you provide it to us** by using one of the following Site features:

  * When you communicate with us via the _Contact Us_ page, MightyMagoo asks for your name and e-mail address so that you can receive a response.
  * When you use our “Send Game to Friend” feature, MightyMagoo collects the name and email address of you and your friend. We will only send your friend a one time email inviting them to visit the site and check out the game that you had sent them. We do not retain their Personal Information for any purpose.
  * (we do not collect any PII when games are submitted)

AdThis Widget

If you choose to use our referral service to send a game to a friend using the AdThis Widget, AdThis will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We do not collect or store the information collected through the AdThis widget, please read their privacy policy regarding the collection and use of this information. We also use the AdThis widget in order to allow you to share links to our site on various third party Web Sites. Please note that you will be taken to these third party domains and asked to login to your account in order to share links about MightyMagoo. MightyMagoo does not have any access to this information.

**  
If you do not want us to collect your PII as described above or to use and share your PII as described further below in this Policy, you should NOT provide it to us through any of the MightyMagoo features described above. By providing us with your PII using any of these features, you are authorizing our use and sharing of your PII as described in this Policy and any subsequent revisions to this Policy that we may publish on the Site.  
**

**  
Updating Your Personally Identifiable Information.  
**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, amend, or remove it by emailing our Customer Support at  

**Children’s Privacy**

MightyMagoo and the content available or emails delivered in connection withMightyMagoo, are neither intended for, nor directed to, nor to be accessed by, persons under the age of 13. **We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under 13 years of age.**

**Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information**

Duck Play LLC reserves the right to use PII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided as stated above; (2) for the purposes disclosed at the time such information is provided; or (3) as disclosed in this Policy.

In addition, if Duck Play LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your PII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on the MightyMagoo home page for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your PII.

Duck Play LLC reserves the right to disclose PII as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

**  
Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
As with manywebsites, when you visit MightyMagoo, MightyMagoo automatically gathers certain NPII based on your computer information and stores it in log files. This type of technical and statistical information is used to customize your experience at MightyMagoo, to help us improve the quality of MightyMagoo and to make your visits to MightyMagoo easy, convenient and fun. MightyMagoo also collects your IP (Internet protocol) address to help diagnose problems with the Site server and for Site administration purposes.

In addition to the general collection of NPII by the Site, the Software downloaded by Premium Users tracks HTML on the web pages Users visit in order to deliver ads contextually, and track URLs, web pages and/or search queries to deliver display ads. **If at any time, a Premium User no longer wants the Software to collect NPII or to deliver customized advertising, s/he may deactivate the Software which will uninstall the Software and its associated monitoring technologies**. The directions for uninstalling the Software are set forth below in the section entitled “Deactivate Software.”

Finally, we and some of our Third Party Advertisers as well as third party ad servers also use cookies, web beacons, clear GIFs, and other monitoring technologies to gather anonymous information. The most common of these technologies are described in more detail below.

Cookies. Cookies are small data files that the MightyMagoo server places on an individual’s computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Site and the Company. We do not tie any PII to the cookies that we set. Cookies also enable us, or our Third Party Advertisers, to use anonymous behavioral profiles and demographic inferences to increase the relevance of online ads that Premium Members receive. Some MightyMagoo ads include “web beacons” and some of our Third Party Advertisers may include web beacons on some of their web pages at our request. These web beacons allow us to access the cookies we set and provide ad campaign analysis. While some Web browsers allow a User to automatically reject all cookies or be notified when a cookie is about to be placed on the User’s computer, disabling this feature may compromise the efficiency and added services that our cookies provide. If you ever uninstall the Software, no Duck Play LLC cookies or tracking assets will remain. **. The use of cookies by Third Party Advertisers or ad servers is not subject to this Policy, but is subject to those third parties’ respective privacy policies. If you have a question about such third parties’ privacy policies, you will have to go to their websites for more information and/or contact them directly**.

Clear GIFs. We employ or our third party business partners may employ a common technology known as a “Clear GIF” or “1-by-1 Pixel” on the Site and in e-mail communications with Users. A Clear GIF, or “graphic interface format” is a small graphic (in fact, truly a 1×1 pixel) that is placed on the Site or in an e-mail. The GIFs do not contain any PII but they, provide us with important information about how Users use MightyMagoo and respond to e-mail messages. With this information, MightyMagoo or our Business Partners are better able to track the performance of certain promotions and understand the effectiveness of particular creative presentations. We may also allow our Third Party Advertisers the ability to use GIFs on the Site solely to track Premium Users who link from the Third Party Advertisers’ respective sites to MightyMagoo, but this ability to track does not allow the Third Party Advertisers access to Premium User PII.

**Use and Sharing of Non-Personally Identifiable Information (NPII)**

Duck Play LLC shares NPII with our Business Partners in order to customize the services they and MightyMagoo provide to you. And of course, we may also disclose any of the NPII collected through MightyMagoo or the Software in order to (1) comply with applicable laws, (2) respond to governmental inquiries, (3) comply with valid legal process, or (4) protect our rights and property or thatof or our Users.

**Security**

We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect Information from unauthorized access and improper use. We keep Information on servers that are protected by firewalls and located in a physically secure facility accessible only to authorized our employees. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though, that, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and any connection to MightyMagoo or information transmitted to us or to MightyMagoo will be at your own risk.

**Opt-Out of MightyMagoo E-mails**

If you are receiving emails from MightyMagoo, it is because we understood from your participation on our Site that you were interested in receiving ongoing information from us. If at any point you no longer want to receive emails from MightyMagoo, you may at any time go to the Unsubscribe page on MightyMagoo and following the ‘opt out’ directions there. If you have any questions about the opt-out process, you can contact us at [MightyMagoo Support](mailto:support@mightymagoo.com). Also,, please note that if we have already shared your information with one of our Business Partners, unsubscribing from our list will not prevent these third parties from emailing you. You will have to send an opt-out request to those third parties directly. Opportunities to “opt out” from receiving emails are usually found on these companies’ websites or within each of their email communications.

**Links from the Site**

MightyMagoo provides links to the websites of many of our Business Partners. If you link to any of these third party Web sites, our privacy policy will not apply to your use of, and activities on, those sites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these sites, including their privacy policies. Duck Play LLC shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, these sites. All inquiries concerning the use of PII by a third party must be communicated to that third party and not to MightyMagoo or Duck Play LLC.

**Deactivate Software**

Premium Users who have downloaded the Software and who do not want their NPII collected as described above should immediately deactivate the Software. You may deactivate the Software by going to the [Deactivate page](http://www.mightymagoo.com/deactivate/) and following the directions to remove the Software from your computer, or by selecting the appropriate entry in your Control Panel using the “Add or Remove Programs” icon. Deactivating the Software means that you will no longer have access to the Premium Games on the Site.

**  
QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS  
**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy or its implementation, please email us at [MightyMagoo Support](mailto:support@mightymagoo.com).
